ranktrackr.com 2017-12-12

# Privacy Policy | RankTrackr

## Information collection and processing

In the course of using our Site and service (together, the “Service”) we ask you to provide us with certain personal information. The personal information that we collect, process and file, inter alia, is:

  * Your contact information; e.g. your name, company name, email address, postal address and phone number.
  * Your email address used to login to your PayPal account or other financial accounts when using the Service to make or receive payments. We use PayPal, and possibly other services, and they may also collect and process personal information, such as Credit Card information. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of these services.
  * Feedback from users about their experience with other users of the Service. Please note that any feedback you provide will be publicly viewable via the Service.
  * When you visit our Site, whether as a registered or nonregistered user our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. This log data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol, IP address, browser type, browser software version or the webpage you were visiting before you came to our Site, pages of our Site that you visit, the time spent on those pages, information you search for on our Site, access times and dates, and other statistics. In addition to this, we may use third party services that collect, monitor and analyse this type of information with the purpose of increasing our Site’s functionality and user-friendliness, to better tailor it to our visitors’ needs, and in some cases to detect suspicious activity. These third party service providers have their own privacy policies addressing how they use such information. We use cookies to record this information. See our cookie policy below.

## Use of personal information

We use your personal information to provide the Service, complete your transactions, and administer your inquiries. We only use your personal information to contact you with our newsletters, marketing or promotional materials if you have given us your prior consent. If you decide at any time that you no longer wish to receive such communications from us, please follow the unsubscribe instructions provided in any of the communications or contact us at info@ranktrackr.com. We may also use general information from your use of our service for statistical analysis and product development.

## Disclosure

### Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement

We will only disclose information about you to government or law enforcement officials or private parties if we are obliged to do it or believe it necessary in order to respond to claims and legal process to protect the property and rights of RankTrackr or a third party, to protect the safety of the public or any person, or to prevent or stop activity we may consider to be, or to pose a risk of being, illegal, unethical or legally actionable activity.

## Right of access, right to rectification and deletion

You have the right of access to information relating to you. You also have the right to request rectification and under certain circumstances deletion of information that we have registered about you. Please contact us at info@ranktrackr.com.

## Security

The security of your personal information is important to us. To ensure your security we encrypt all passwords used on the Site.

## Links to Other Sites

Our Site contains links to other websites. If you choose to click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party’s website. These other websites may place their own cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information from you. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit.

## Changes in the Privacy Policy

RankTrackr may at any time and without notice make changes to its Privacy Policy with future effect.

## Our Cookie Policy

Like many websites, we use “cookies” to collect information. A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a user’s computer, and that the user’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. It is for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies for two purposes. First, we utilize persistent cookies to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Site and to track your compliance with our marketplace policies. Second, we utilize session ID cookies to enable certain features of the Site, to better understand how you interact with the Site and to monitor aggregate usage by RankTrackr Users and web traffic routing on the Site. Unlike persistent cookies, session cookies are deleted from your computer when you log off from the Site and Service and then close your browser. You can instruct your browser, by changing its options, to stop accepting cookies or to prompt you before accepting a cookie from the websites you visit. See the guidance below. If you do not accept cookies, however, you may not be able to use all portions of the Site or all functionality of the Service. When you visit our website, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. We use cookies to collect log data. For more information see Information collecting and processing above. Third party cookies: We use third party services to analyse the use of our site for statistical purposes. Guidance in removing cookies from your browser: Contact us at info@ranktrackr.com.

## Choice of law

Any disputes involving RankTrackr about the use of the Service and this Privacy Policy are subject to Slovenian law and the Ljubljana City Court has exclusive jurisdiction to determine any such dispute.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at info@ranktrackr.com or by mail addressed to Kundi d.o.o., Gmajna 42a, Slovenj Gradec.
